Test Cleanup Utility
Written by Thomas Landry for use and distrubution by the Orange Unified School District
-----
The purpose of this utility is to automatically close any apps that may interfer with the ability for
testing browser to run. The goal is to be able to have students simple click on the utility before taking
a test and not have to close processes themselves.
-----
To use this utility, three seperate files are needed.
The utility executable itself.
And a .csv file named 'TestCleanupApps.csv'
A .config file named 'FileSource.config'
-----
The TestCleanupApps.csv file will serve as a master record of the apps that the program will close and
should be placed in a central location on the network where anyone has access privilages. The file should
conatain the name of the process AS IT APPEARS IN POWERSHELL when using the Get-Process cmdlt, the date it
was added to the record, and a description of it. For example a single row might look like:

Teams,05/08/1945,The Teams client in windows

This utility will not be able to correctly close an application if the Porcess Name is not correct.
-----
The FileSource.config file should be placed in the ProgramData/TestCleanupScript folder and should only contain
the path to the TestCleanupApps.csv file on the network. For example:

\\School-Server\softwarepush\TestCleanupUtility

Do not include TestCleanupApps.csv in the path.
-----
